<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Tank Studios]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Blogging about my walk with Jesus in a modern world]]></description>
        <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net/</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 19:28:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://blog.tankstudios.net//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 19:16:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arguing Wrong: Why I said We Should Not Fast]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    Sometimes it is fun to argue for something you do not actually believe, and one time I did just that.
    The argument I made: we, as followers of Christ, should not fast.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>I want to clarify; I believe we should fast. Fasting is a great discipline.</strong> Maybe
    I&#39;ll talk about it in a future blog post. But for now, I&#39;ll just explain the time I argued otherwise.
</p>
<h3>Why I Entered the Argument</h3>
<p>
    In college, four years ago, a friend of mine asked, &quot;What do you think of fasting?&quot;
    I thought briefly and responded, &quot;I don&#39;t like it.&quot; My friend, as is to be expected, asked, &quot;Why?&quot; I responded, 
    &quot;Because I do not believe it is biblical.&quot;
</p>
<p>
    I&#39;m not sure why I responded that way. I was mostly being silly. <strong>I enjoyed making off the wall statements,
    and I was not at all worried about swaying my friend to believe something crazy.</strong> She is a devout
    follower of Christ, and she was at least as well-versed in the Word as I was. We regularly had
    good conversations about what it looks like to follow Jesus, and I guess I decided it was time to throw a curveball
    into our discussion.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>When I made this claim about fasting being unbiblical, I had no basis at all.</strong> 
    In fact, I could think up plenty of reasons why fasting <em>is</em> biblical. However, I made the claim;
    therefore, I needed to come up with a way to back it up.
</p>
<p>
    As expected, the friend once again asked, &quot;Why?&quot; And thus it began.
</p>
<h3>Why You Shouldn&#39;t Fast</h3>
<p>
    <strong>In case you are only joining us at this header and have skipped everything before it, I believe we should fast.</strong>
    If you are confused about the disjoint between the header and that sentence, don&#39;t jump in at the middle of a 
    blog post next time!...but don&#39;t feel too bad; I do it all the time.
</p>
<p>
    My argument stemmed from a question asked of Jesus in Matthew:
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
        Then the disciples of John came to Him, saying, &quot;Why do we and the Pharisees fast, but your
        disciples do not fast?&quot; And Jesus said to them, &quot;Can the wedding guests mourn as long as
        the bridegroom is with them? The days will come when the bridegroom is taken away from them, and then they will fast.&quot;
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>Matthew 9:14-16</strong> (ESV)
</p>
<p>
    I claimed that here Jesus tells us we should not fast. He tells us specifically that we should not fast
    as long as He is with us. Well, is Jesus not with us? Matthew 28:20, &quot;And behold, I (Jesus) am with you always to the end of the age.&quot;
    Again in Hebrews 13:5, &quot;I will never leave you nor forsake you.&quot;
</p>
<p>
    If Jesus is with us, why would we mourn? We should celebrate! There were three days &quot;when the bridegroom was taken away from them;&quot;
    those were the days to fast. But He came back, and now we no longer need to fast!
</p>
<h3>How I was Immediately Defeated</h3>
<p>
    I think my friend humored me for a few minutes. She asked some questions, and I delved in a bit deeper. <strong>But suddenly,
    realization struck her, and she asked, &quot;Didn&#39;t they fast in Acts?&quot;</strong>
</p>
<p>
    I responded, &quot;Yes they did. I lose the argument.&quot; In the process of developing my argument, 
    I had already found the verse to completely refute it: Acts 13:2-3,
    &quot;While they were worshiping the Lord and <em>fasting</em>...then after <em>fasting</em> and praying...&quot; <strong>My argument
    immediately falls apart because I was claiming the disciples should not have fasted after Jesus&#39; resurrection,
    yet here they are seen fasting!</strong>
</p>
<h3>What&#39;s the Point?</h3>
<p>
    There is a reason I tell this story. It is not to show intelligence in coming up with an argument for something
    I don&#39;t believe. It&#39;s not to show you that I did not &quot;rightly handle the Word of truth&quot; as commanded in
    Timothy (2 Tim. 2: 15).
</p>
<p>
    <strong>I tell this story to show how easy it is to make a convincing argument about anything.</strong>
    The Bible is a big book! Anybody who knows a fair amount of it can pull verses from the left, right, Old Testament
    and New Testament, throw them all at you at once without any context, and pummel you into submission in an argument.
    Again, that is a poor way to &quot;rightly handle the Word of truth,&quot; but it can be done.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>However, most bad arguments from Scripture can quickly and easily be countered by Scripture itself.</strong> I am <em>not</em> saying
    the Bible contradicts itself, but I am saying that people can twist anything to make it fit what they want it to mean.
    And if we know Scripture as well as my friend did, we can see through the falsehoods. Sometimes it may be a little
    more difficult that it was for her, but the better we see the full picture of the Bible, the better we can
    hear each verse in context. Then we will know when somebody is using that verse out of context.
</p>
<p>
    Any good teacher will say, &quot;Test what I tell you.&quot;
    But I could say that and immediately teach something crazy, and people who never read the Bible
    will have no idea! Saying &quot;Test me&quot; gives me free credibility if I know it will never be done! 
</p>
<p>
    <strong>My point, then, is to <em>read the Bible for yourself</em>. Be in the Word regularly.</strong> &quot;Be renewed by the transforming of your mind&quot; (Rom 12:2).
    Be in the Word that never returns void (Is. 55:11). Be in the Word that is &quot;living and active, sharper than a double-edged sword,
    piercing to the division of soul and of spirit, of joints and of marrows, and discerning the thoughts and intentions of the heart&quot; (Heb. 4:12)!
    You do not want to be &quot;tossed to and fro by the waves and carried about by every wind of doctriine, by human cunning,
    by craftiness in deceitful schemes.&quot; (Eph 4:14).
</p>
<p>
    If you are in Christ, you do not need a teacher. Teachers can help guide, but the Spirit is your teacher. 1 Cor. 2 explains
    how nobody can know the mind of God except His Spirit, and that His Spirit searches the depths of God and teaches us, giving
    us the mind of Christ (2 Cor 2:10-16)! And we are told in 1 John 2:27 that we have no need of anyone to teach us, but that
    his anointing teaches us about everything!
</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>
    <strong>Hopefully this has increased your desire to spend time with Christ in the Word even more.</strong> There are so many benefits. Steadfast confidence 
    in the truth is just one of many. Please continue in your time in the Word.
</p>
<p>
    Also, though I have spent a lot of time discussing the importance of time individually in the Word, <strong>there is massive benefit
    to spending time in a local church with a community of believers.</strong> Hebrews regularly explains the importance of having both
    fellow believers to regularly encourage you and authority to correct and protect you. <strong>In the end, the author commands
    us to meet together!</strong> Heb. 10:24, &quot;And let us consider how to stir up one another to love and good works, not neglecting
    to meet together, as is the habit of some, but encouraging one another, and all the more as you see the Day drawing near.&quot;
</p>
<p>
    I hope you have enjoyed this story! I really appreciate the time you all take to read what I write. I greatly enjoy it, and I learn a lot
    in the process of writing these posts out. <strong>I hope you enjoy reading them as much as I enjoy writing them!</strong>
</p>
<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/arguing-wrong.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/arguing-wrong.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 19:27:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I Am Weak]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    I am weak, and I&#39;m not referring to my physical strength. Well...to be fair, I can include my physical strength in that weakness.
    I put all my effort into running instead of strength. Therefore, when I have a slight head start on the strong guy who wants to destroy
    my face, I should be alright.
</p>
<p>
    Lets start over. <strong>I am weak.</strong> I am weak physically, but I am also weak in other aspects of my life. For instance, I am unable to multitask. If
    I am driving a car and simultaneously having an in-depth conversation with the passenger, I will likely end up driving us to my home. Why? Home is the
    path of least resistance. My brain cannot have the conversation and make directional decisions, so it chooses the path it takes most regularly.
    Michelle often corrects my directions.
</p>
<p>
    Also, I am a shy, reserved person. Mingling is rough on me. I&#39;ve found that if you carry something, keep moving, and put on a determined look, people
    are less likely to notice that you&#39;re simply moving in a large circle around the mingling area and not actually talking to anybody. But I used
    to have more than just mingling miseries. For instance, my freshman year in college, I went a full week not having a conversation
    with a single person. I holed out in my dorm, in the dark, leaving only for food and classes.  Good times.
</p>
<p>
    And I could go on. I&#39;m not an audial learner. I get extremely grumpy when I am both hungry and bored. I&#39;m not observant. I forget details.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>Most people are ashamed, or at least saddened, by their weaknesses. However, here I am, happily discussing them with the world. Why would I do that?</strong>
</p>
<h3>Where Weakness Comes From</h3>
<p>
    Christians will often declare that weakness is a result of sin. Any physical or mental deficiencies are a result of sin in the world, and they are bad.
    It is believed that, if at all possible, we should try to power through weakness; otherwise, suffer with them as best as possible.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>But what if, sometimes, weaknesses are from God?</strong> Read this:
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
        But Moses said to the Lord, &quot;Oh, my Lord, I am not eloquent, either in the past or since you have spoken to your servant, 
        but I am slow of speech and of tongue.&quot; Then the Lord said to him, &quot;Who has made man&#39;s mouth? Who makes him mute, or deaf, or seeing, or blind? Is it not I, the Lord?&quot;
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>Exodus 4:10-11</strong> (ESV)
</p>
<p>
    Wait, what? When I read this, I was stunned! God just declared that HE makes a man mute, deaf, seeing, and blind. Maybe I should look elsewhere...
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
        As he passed by, he saw a man blind from birth. And his disciples asked him, &quot;Rabbi, who sinned, this man or his parents, that he was born blind?&quot;
        Jesus answered, &quot;It was not that this man sinned, or his parents, but that the works of God might be displayed in him.&quot;
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>John 9:1-3</strong> (ESV)
</p>
<p>
    Here again, this physical defect was not a result of sin, but it instead came from God!
</p>
<h3>How Do We Respond</h3>
<p>
    <strong>So we see that, at least in the above two cases, weakness came from God.</strong> How do we respond to this? Lets look at Paul&#39;s response:
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
         So to keep me from becoming conceited because of the surpassing greatness of the revelations, a thorn was given me in the flesh, a messenger of Satan to harass me, 
         to keep me from becoming conceited. Three times I pleaded with the Lord about this, that it should leave me.
         But he said to me, &quot;My grace is sufficient for you, for my power is made perfect in weakness.&quot; 
         Therefore I will boast all the more gladly of my weaknesses, so that the power of Christ may rest upon me. For the sake of Christ, then, I am
         content with weaknesses, insults, hardships, persecutions, and calamities. For when I am weak, then I am strong.
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>2 Cor 12:7-10</strong> (ESV)
</p>
<p>
    Paul has an amazing attitude here! First, he <em>pleads</em> with our Lord to free him from the &quot;thorn.&quot; <strong>We see that it is okay to try to be free from our weakness.</strong> God is the
    Great Healer. He can heal us of any weakness we have, and we should ask Him to! In the story of John 9, Jesus heals the blind man!
    If the issue is physical, we should pray, and we should go see a doctor. If it is mental, we
    should pray and seek wise counsel. If the issue is a personality weakness, we should pray and work towards growing out of the weakness.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>But we notice that He doesn&#39;t always heal.</strong> He didn&#39;t remove the thorn from Paul. He didn&#39;t heal Moses&#39; mouth. Instead, God says, &quot;My grace is sufficient for you,
    for my power is made perfect in weakness.&quot;
</p>
<p>
    This paints a beautiful picture of weakness. <strong>Where we find ourselves strong, we completely forget our desperate need for God.</strong> In our
    weakness, we learn the truth of Acts 17:24 - 25, &quot;The God who made the world and everything in it, being Lord of heaven and earth, does not live
    in temples made by man, nor is he served by human hands, as though he needed anything, since he himself gives to all mankind life and breath and everything.&quot;
    We cannot even <em>breathe</em> without God! Talk about weakness!
</p>
<p>
    <strong>So instead of sinking into a depressed state or considering ourselves worthless in our weakness, we should instead discover the great power and gift God has
    given us in our weakness! In our weakness, Christ&#39;s power is made perfect!</strong> For example, I told you all about my shyness. Can you imagine a person like that
    wanting to do overseas missions? What about sing in front of a church? Trust me, that would have never have happened without Christ&#39;s power working in my life.
    Every conversation I have is proof of Christ&#39;s power in me. 
</p>
<p>
    <strong>Let us look at our weaknesses as a way to show off Christ&#39;s power! Every situation is different, but every situation is a chance to point to the glory of the
    One who gives to all mankind life and breath and everything.</strong> Examine yourself: what are your weaknesses? Remember what Paul says to the Corinthians, &quot;But God
    chose what is foolish in the world to shame the wise; God chose what is weak in the world to shame the strong; God chose what is low and despised in the world, even
    the things that are not, to bring to nothing things that are, so that no human being might boast in the presence of God. And because of Him you are in Christ Jesus,
    who became to us wisdom from God, righteousness and sanctification and redemption, so that as it is written, &#39;Let the one who boasts, boast in the Lord.&#39;&quot; (1 Cor 1:27-31, ESV).
</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>
    To those who are hurting in their weaknesses, I hope this gives you comfort. Christ&#39;s power is ready to be made perfect in you. When you are weak, then
    you are strong. <strong>As the foolish of the world, as the weak in the world, as the low and despised...let us go out and proclaim
    Him who makes us strong.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/weaknesses.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/weaknesses.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2016 03:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Become a Deeper Person: Choosing King Size Over Fun Size]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    Why are the smallest candy bars called &quot;fun&quot; size?  I&#39;ve never understood.
    Eating chocolate is fun. Therefore, the bigger the candy bar, the more
    fun I&#39;m having!
</p>
<p>
    However, we seem to live in a fun-sized culture
    when it comes to consuming information.  We don&#39;t want the king size
    information! We consume quick bites, taking in
    a few views on the situation, getting the feel for it, and calling it
    good.
</p>
<p>
    And really, that&#39;s not bad! <strong>There is <em>so</em> much information out there,
    how can we expect to dive deep into any of it?</strong>  I am exceedingly thankful
    for the wealth of information at arms reach, and in many
    topics I am happy to get the gist of the discussion and move on with
    life.
</p>
<p>
    However, if we leave it at that, we remain shallow thinkers.  <strong>All our
    information came from what we uncovered in a bite-size fashion rather
    than giving a subject time to dig deep into, looking at opposing viewpoints,
    discovering implications on the world around us, and putting the
    information into practice.</strong>
</p>
<h3>Upgrading to King Size</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>
    No matter how busy you may think you are, you must find time for reading, or surrender yourself to self-chosen ignorance.
</p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>-Confucious, <a href="http://www.dictionary-quotes.com/no-matter-how-busy-you-may-think-you-are-you-must-find-time-for-reading-or-surrender-yourself-to-self-chosen-ignorance-confucius/">Source</a></strong>
</p>
<p>
    Discovering subjects in-depth solidifies us in our beliefs. When we hear
    a variety of viewpoints, we can pull from a diverse range of opinions and develop our own.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>If we only consume shallow information, we either become fiercely loyal to
    a cause without any ability to defend it, or we are swayed to and fro by the
    last person who spoke.</strong> As we delve into a topic, we learn to defend our stance.
    We struggle through counterpoints, discovering and addressing concerns before
    anybody confronts us.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>The shallower we remain in a subject, the more we are outsourcing our beliefs.</strong>  We
    let a politician, blogger, celebrity, friend, etc. become our foundation.
    We might even be able to regurgitate their arguments. However, those arguments can be
    quickly stomped on by anyone who has thought through a topic on their own.
</p>
<p>
    Despite becoming more solidified, going deeper into a topic helps us become more understanding. <strong>When we see a variety of viewpoints,
    we will become much slower in claiming people are idiots.</strong> We will be less inclined to think, &quot;How could anybody believe that!?&quot;
    Instead, we&#39;ll have put ourselves in that person&#39;s beliefs and seen the reasons why they believe what they do. Admittedly, some beliefs
    are still worth being called insane, but at least we&#39;ll have firmer reasons other than, &quot;It&#39;s not what I believe.&quot;
</p>
<h3>The Mouth Speaks From the Input to the Heart</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>
    The good person out of the good treasure of his heart produces good, and the evil person out of his evil treasure produces evil, for out of the abundance of the heart his mouth speaks.
</p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>-Jesus, Luke 6:45</strong>
</p>
<p>
    It is difficult for some to have deep conversations with others. There are many factors that come into play - shyness, time, comfort - but <strong>if we find that our conversations
    with close friends and family are ever only scratching surface level, perhaps the fault lies in what we put into our hearts.</strong> Are we spending our days entertained?
    If tv shows, sports, funny videos, and work are all that we ever discuss, maybe we should find new inputs?
</p>
<p>
    I find the more in-depth I am reading, the more I am moving in life. <strong>I stop spending every day entertaining myself until bedtime, but I begin actively
    seeking better ways to live my life. And as I go through these changes, I have the opportunity to deepen life discussions. I am thinking deeply about my life,
    and I can ask friends and family their thoughts on the topic.</strong>
</p>
<blockquote>
<p>
    The more you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you&#39;ll go.
</p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>-Dr. Seuss, <em>I Can Read With My Eyes Shut!</em></strong>
</p>
<h3>The Most Important Read</h3>
<p>
    I could talk much more on this subject. However, you are reading the fun size information! Since I have to keep
    it fun size, I want to move along to an application of all this information.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>From the two points above, I hope you can see the dire importance for the Christian to read the Word of God.</strong> First, how are we to know
    we are not living in complete ignorance? If we are simply hearing a fun size sermon from the same source Sunday after Sunday, how do we
    know we are not living in &quot;willful ignorance?&quot; <strong>Our only defense is to discover for ourselves!</strong>
</p>
<p>
    But the second point makes reading the Bible even more important. <strong>We must read God&#39;s Word because His Word is the absolute best thing we
    can put into our hearts.</strong> &quot;Do not be conformed to the world but be transformed by the renewing of your mind&quot; (Rom. 12:2). As we pour
    God&#39;s truth into our hearts day after day we begin to move. <strong>Thirty minute fun-size sermons are quickly overtaken by the
    wave of entertainment and news. We must combat this by filling our lives full of Him. Our hearts will be changed. Our conversations
    will be changed. Our view of the world will be changed. Avoiding God&#39;s Word is avoiding the most powerful method of change towards
    Christ we have!</strong>
</p>
<p>
    Change comes slowly; sentence by sentence, we are transformed little by little. A tree planted by a stream does not grow overnight. But when it gets
    a steady intake of water, see how big it can get and what fruit it can bear! Compare that to a tree that gets only enough water to stay alive.
</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>
    Before I go, a quick clarification on that last point. <strong>Reading the Word should never be in the mindset simply to gain more knowledge.</strong> The goal
    is to spend time with God, letting Him pour His truths into our life, getting to know Him better, growing a deeper and deeper love for Him, and
    transforming our lives into ones that are effective for His Kingdom. And all this can only be done through the Spirit that explains the Word to us
    and enacts the change in our lives.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>I hope I have encouraged everyone to deepen their knowledge, through reading or some other medium</strong> - first, the Bible, then on all kinds of subjects. The deeper we are,
    the more we can relate to people. The more we can relate to people, the better we can love them. The better we can love, the more God
    is using us in &quot;Thy Kingdom come, Thy will be done, on Earth as it is in Heaven&quot; (Matt 6:10).
</p>
<p>
    I&#39;d love to hear thoughts on this topic, as well as some of your favorite book recommendations! Thank you for reading.
</p>
<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/why-to-read.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/why-to-read.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 04:36:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Biggest Regret]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    Everybody makes mistakes.  The bigger they are, the more painful
    the memory. Many people live with a motto such as
    &quot;no regrets&quot; or simply recognize that mistakes create the person
    that exists today and hope that&#39;s a good thing.
</p>

<p>
    I agree with those concepts. However, I do regret a few actions.  I&#39;m thankful for the person I became, by the
    grace bought by Jesus Christ, learning through those actions. But I still wish
    that I had already been the kind of person that did not make those mistakes to
    begin with.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>Here is the story that I regret the most.</strong>
</p>

<p><h3>The Valediction</h3></p>
<p>
    When I was in middle school, I went to a high school graduation. Afterward, I asked
    my dad why some students got to speak. He explained that the valedictorians, those
    who made a 4.0 GPA, deliver a farewell speech at the graduation.
</p>
<p>
    &quot;I&#39;m going to be a valedictorian.&quot; I then decided. And I succeeded.
</p>
<p>
    Years later, I began preparing for the speech. I thought and thought over what message
    I wanted to share. At the time, <strong>I was not a follower of Christ.
    Therefore, God got a shoutout at the beginning of my speech and that was it.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    I was pleased with the final product.  <strong>The speech explained the importance of goals
    in a persons life. When a person makes goals, they have direction.  Without goals,
    we wander aimlessly in life, never accomplishing anything.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    My final line and conclusion, &quot;A life without goals - a life without purpose - is no
    life at all.&quot;
</p>
<h3>The Response</h3>
<p>
    Everybody loved it. Some teachers said it was the best valediction they had ever heard. 
    Everyone I knew approved of my message.
</p>
<p>
    The message I shared was the message by which I lived. I went to college with many
    goals and plans for my life. Graduate, get an awesome job, marry, have kids, enjoy!
</p>
<p>
    <strong>...And my first year of college was miserable.</strong> By the middle of the second semester
    I was looking towards all these goals I set and asking, &quot;What&#39;s the point? I&#39;ve set
    all these goals for my life, but do they really bring meaning?  I&#39;m just going to
    die, right?  Who cares if I get rich or get married? And will I <em>really</em> enjoy
    doing the same job for 40 years?  Is giving up that much of my life for money really
    having a life?&quot;
</p>
<p>
    <strong>It was starting to sound like the life I had chosen, and the life I preached at my
    valediction, was &quot;no life at all&quot; as well.</strong>
</p>
<h3>The Life</h3>
<p>
    <strong>These thoughts finally led to my knees before my
    Lord,</strong> declaring that I am a terrible God, that He is worthy of all honor and glory,
    that I have been rebelling against Him and rejecting Him my whole life, that I
    deserve punishment, and that I need Him to save me from the just judgment that
    I deserve.
</p>
<p>
    And He did save me. <strong>I died to my sins with Him on the cross, canceling the record of debt
    that stood against me (Col 2:12-15), and it is no longer I who live, but
    Christ who lives in me, and the life I now live in the flesh, I live by faith
    in the Son of God, who loved me and gave Himself for me! (Gal 2:20)</strong>
</p>
<p>
    I have found true Life in the past 7 years.  Goals do not bring life. Money
    does not bring life. Entertainment doesn&#39;t, people don&#39;t, sin doesn&#39;t.  <strong>They
    all bring only death. But Jesus is the Way, the Truth, and the Life (John 14:6)
    and He has come the we may have life, and life in abundance! (John 10:10)</strong>
</p>
<h3>The Regret</h3>
<p>
    My biggest regret is that speech. I stood before a captive audience of more than a thousand
    people, hanging on to my every word, seeking to hear the advice that I would
    give as they go out into the world. 
</p>
<p>
    <strong>There, I offered them life...a life full of toiling after goals they create based
    on their own desires, and a life that would be found wanting in the end, bearing
    no eternal significance.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    <strong>If I could have it back, I would spend the time pointing them back
    to the true bringer of life, Jesus Christ</strong>, begging them on behalf of Christ,
    be reconciled to God, for He made Him who knew no sin to be sin on our behalf,
    so that we might become the righteousness of God in Him. (2 Cor 5:20-21)
</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>
    So there it is: my biggest regret. I hope any who took my advice
    to heart ended up walking the same road I did, leading straight into
    Christ. 
</p>
<p>
    I know that one day I will give an account to God for all I have done:
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
        For the word of God is living and active,
        sharper than any two-edged sword, piercing to the division of soul
        and of spirit, of joints and of marrow, and discerning the thoughts
        and intentions of the heart. Nothing in all creation is hidden from God&#39;s sight.
        Everything is uncovered and laid bare before the eyes of him to whom we must give
        account.
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>Hebrews 4:13-14</strong>
</p>
<p>
    <strong>But thankfully, as stated above, Christ has made me innocent. I am
    free from my guilt</strong>, and instead can say with Paul:
</p>
<blockquote>
    <p>
        But one thing I do: forgetting what lies behind and straining forward to what
        lies ahead, I press on toward the goal
        for the prize of the upward call of God in Christ Jesus.
    </p>
</blockquote>
<p>
    <strong>Philippians 3:13-14</strong>
</p>

<p>
    As always, I love to hear anybody&#39;s feedback, comments, or questions!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/biggest-regret.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/biggest-regret.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 22:10:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Riding a Horse with the Blessed Sovereign]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    I rode a horse two weeks ago.  It was only my second time to ride
    without a guide holding  the reigns.
</p>

<p>
    The first time riding, I had little confidence in my ability, and the horse was in command.<br>    This plan did not work out in my benefit.  The horse walked between two trees that were very close together.
    The trees were far enough apart for the horse to squeeze through, but they were too close to let my legs get past!
    <strong>Not being willing to control the horse, I let him walk
    me straight into the trees!</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Thankfully, I did not get pushed from his back.  Instead,
    I managed to put the horse in reverse and get out of the trees.  Afterwards, I kept a firmer hand on the reigns.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>My second outing went better.</strong>
</p>

<h3>Part One: The Crying Girl and the Mountain Climbing Horses</h3>

<p>
    Michelle and I are the last to get in the saddle.  <strong>I&#39;m riding Bill and Michelle is on Daisy.</strong>
    As we get comfortable, our fearless leader, a 12 year old girl, gives
    us instructions on controlling the horse.
</p>

<p><img class="small-image" src="../img/horse-riding/horse-stand.jpg" /></p>
<center class="img-caption"><small>Michelle by her horse Daisy</small></center>

<p>
    The scene is what one would expect on a group horse ride: a gorgeous day at
    perfect temperature, a leader giving instructions, a few dogs circling the group,
    11 people atop horses in a semi-circle, each hanging on to every word in hopes it might save their life, 
    <strong>and one 16 year old, sobbing, clearly convinced the instructions will
    not save her from her impending doom.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    I try to act as if the crying girl does not exist, realizing her
    three friends can comfort her much better than I. If I were in
    her shoes, I also would prefer others to ignore my existence. <strong>As
    the ride begins, it is clear that neither her friends nor
    my valiant efforts at ignorance will cheer her.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    The girl and her boyfriend end up right in front of me.  He is
    speaking soft words to her from his horse.  <strong>His horse, however,
    did not get the memo of kindness. Apparently the two horses
    get close to each other, and I watch as the boyfriend&#39;s horse
    kicks the girl&#39;s horse!</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Thinking back on it, perhaps the horse did get the memo, and it is just not skilled at
    awkward social interactions.  <strong>In any case.
    I am thrust into an awkward social interaction myself.</strong>
    The girl falls behind me, but her boyfriend and two other
    friends are stuck in front of me due to the narrow trail.  The result:
    constant stares and regular words of encouragement
    passing by me to the crying girl. <strong>Caught previously
    ignoring the girl&#39;s existence, I am now offered
    the same treatment.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Eventually the girl begins to cheer up.  In fact, she even smiles! <strong>However, the trail,
    expecting unskilled horseman to just be gaining confidence, decides to
    throw us a deep incline.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    The horses are now wondering why we are expecting them to behave like
    mountain goats.  They turn sideways, inching step by step downhill.  I hear
    the girl stifle a cry behind me. We soon discover that the horses are experts in
    mountain climbing!  They head down the hill at a steady pace without incident.
</p>

<h3>Part 2: The Beauty of Nature and Cowdogs</h3>
<p>
    As we traverse this steep hill, I realize how much I am loving this experience! The horses are
    carrying full grown people on their back down a hill I probably couldn&#39;t
    safely traverse on my legs, and they are pros! The ride is full of excitement.  <strong>And as
    we break free of the mountain and into more open fields, the horses begin to trot.
    Even the girl can&#39;t hold back laughter as we move through the plain, enjoying
    the sun.</strong>
</p>

<img class="small-image" src="../img/horse-riding/ryan-horse.jpg" />
<center class="img-caption"><small>Ryan riding Bill</small></center>

<p>
    The rest of the trip we are treated to grand views.  The ranch is in Broken Bow, and the owner&#39;s
    property is beautiful. <strong>Being cooped up in cities for so long now, it&#39;s easy to forget
    what it&#39;s like to be surrounded by nature!</strong>
</p>

<img class="small-image" src="../img/horse-riding/mountains.jpg" />
<center class="img-caption"><small>The view of the mountains</small></center>

<img class="small-image" src="../img/horse-riding/michelle-horse.jpg" />
<center class="img-caption"><small>Michelle on her horse</small></center>

<p>
    <strong>In this area, the dogs following become comedians.</strong>  They run between our horse&#39;s legs, chasing each other. When we
    reach the water, one dog is so small he swims through what the horses are easily walking in.
    As he reaches the end, he attempts to jump up on a dry rock, misses by a bit, and tumbles back into the water!
    He immediately gets up and finds another route.
</p>

<p>
    Then we get to see the dogs at their funniest moment.  We pass a herd of cattle, and the dogs decide
    to chase them down!  Do you remember the scene in The Lion King where Pumbaa barrels into
    a crowd of vultures?  <strong>This is similar, except it&#39;s like Timon chasing a crowd of Pumbaas!</strong>
</p>

<p>
    The cows run full speed away from the dogs, but one cow can&#39;t get away from a certain dog!  The dog chases
    right on the heels of the cow.  The dog is clearly having the time of its life!  The cow on the other hand...
</p>

<p>
    After a complete hour, we arrive safely back at the starting location.  <strong>We all had a great time, including the
    previously terrified girl!</strong>
</p>

<h3>Conclusion: Our Blessed God</h3>

<p>
    Recently, I memorized 1 Timothy 6:15.  It begins with &quot;He is the blessed and only Sovereign, the King of
    Kings and the Lord of Lords.&quot; As we were trotting along in silence, I decided to spend some time
    meditating on that verse, specifically what it means that God is &quot;blessed.&quot;
</p>

<p>
    Working with the understanding that &quot;blessed&quot; is roughly synonymous to the word &quot;happy,&quot; I considered the 
    happiness of God.  The atmosphere was very timely.  Because God is omnipresent (Psalms 33:13-14),
    He was with us during that ride. I considered how pleasing the trip must have been to Him.  He created all
    nature: the sun, the trees, and the horses. And He gave us dominion over them and wants us to enjoy 
    (Psalm 8:6-7).  <strong>The eleven of us were marveling at His creation that day.</strong>  We were laughing in glee
    when the horses picked up the pace or the dogs were acting silly.  We cried in terror at the power
    of the horses.  <strong>And those of us who believe in Him and call on His name were praising Him for the works of
    His hands.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    I am confident watching people enjoy His creation blesses Him as an artist is pleased when others
    enjoy his painting. <strong>In fact, I am confident that God is constantly happy.</strong> His plan of saving
    the nations through Jesus is in motion, in His name, by His power, and with Him with us,
    His followers war against darkness.  And because of His grace, a broken world gets time to
    marvel at the beauty of what He creates.
</p>

<p>
    Any time you look in awe at creation, remember the Creator.  <strong>As the painter puts his personality into the work,
    God has put Himself into the world.</strong> Romans 1:20  states that His eternal power and divine nature are clearly perceived ever since the creation of the world!
    Whenever you are enjoying creation - admiring the stars, riding a horse, enjoying your friends - you are enjoying the Creator of them all.
</p>
<p>
    I&#39;d like to leave you with a Psalm.  I&#39;d love to hear stories of your favorite times enjoying
    God in nature!  Feel free to leave me any comments or feedback!
</p>

<blockquote>
    <p>
        O Lord, our Lord,
            how majestic is your name in all the earth!
        You have set your glory above the heavens.
            Out of the mouth of babes and infants,
        you have established strength because of your foes,
            to still the enemy and the avenger.
    </p>
    <p>

        When I look at your heavens, the work of your fingers,
            the moon and the stars, which you have set in place,
        what is man that you are mindful of him,
            and the son of man that you care for him?
    </p>

    <p>
        Yet you have made him a little lower than the heavenly beings
            and crowned him with glory and honor.
        You have given him dominion over the works of your hands;
            you have put all things under his feet,
        all sheep and oxen,
            and also the beasts of the field,
        the birds of the heavens, and the fish of the sea,
            whatever passes along the paths of the seas.
    </p>

    <p>
        O Lord, our Lord,
            how majestic is your name in all the earth!
    </p>
    <p>
        Psalm 8 (ESV)
    </p>
</blockquote>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/horse-riding.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/horse-riding.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revitalizing My Prayers: Guided by Scripture]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    In prayer, I often find my mind wandering. I can start praying about something I care deeply about, but within a minute,
    I&#39;ve wandered to video games. I also find my prayers to be shallow: &quot;Please do this,&quot; &quot;Thank You for that,&quot;
    &quot;Help me with this.&quot; Are any of those prayers bad? No. <strong>However, I want to talk to and about God that
    expresses a depth of love and emotion toward Him.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    I want to praise God well. For example, a love letter would not look like this:
    &quot;Dear wife, you are awesome. Thank you for everything you do. I hope to treat you well. You are also pretty. Love, husband.&quot;
    While the letter is founded on a deep love of the wife, there is no depth in what the letter says.
    All the words are true, but love letters should express emotion!  The more like Shakespeare, the better!
</p>
<p>
    In the same way, I want to outwardly express the love and joy I have for God. John 3 explains that He already knows the mind and
    hearts of men, but even though He knows, I want to tell Him!  And, I want others to know as well. I love to tell others
    about how great my wife, Michelle, is. Even more so I love to tell others how great my Lord and Savior, Jesus, is!
    And when I tell people, I don&#39;t want my language to be simple and fluffy; I want to speak in a way that they
    feel the emotion with me!
</p>

<p>
    I believe that ability starts with learning to pray.
    Thankfully, I have recently found a way to combat the shallowness of my prayers: the scripture.
</p>

<h3>A Helpful Solution</h3>

<p>
    I read an article on <a href="http://www.desiringgod.org">Desiring God</a> titled <a href="http://www.desiringgod.org/articles/reignite-your-prayer-life"><em>Reignite your Prayer Life</em></a>. This part of the
    article resonated with me:
</p>

<blockquote>
    <p>
        And what is the method of prayer for most Christians? It’s this: When we pray, we tend to say the same old things about the same old things. Sooner or later, that kind of prayer is boring. When prayer is boring, you don’t feel like praying. And when you don’t feel like praying, you don’t pray — at least with any fervency or consistency. Prayer feels much more like duty than delight.
    </p>
    <p>
        The problem is not that we pray about the same old things. To pray about the same things most of the time is normal.
        That’s because our lives tend to consist of the same things from one day to the next. Thankfully, dramatic changes in our
        lives usually don’t occur very often.
    </p>
    <p>
        <strong>No, the problem isn’t that we pray about the same old things; the problem is that we tend to say the same old things about
        the same old things. The result is that we can be talking to the most fascinating Person in the universe about the
        most important things in our lives — and be bored to death.</strong>
    </p>
</blockquote>

<p>
    The author, Don Whitney, proposes a solution for the problem. He recommends praying the Bible. <strong>And, rather than
    praying the words exactly as written and leaving it there, we instead are to let scripture take us by the hand, guiding our
    prayers into its own depths.</strong>
</p>

<h3>How to Start Praying the Bible</h3>

<p>
    With this method, I have come to love the Psalms. Previously I would struggle to focus and enjoy them. What changed?
    <strong>I learned to pray with the Psalmist rather than just read his prayers.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    <strong>Many, if not most, Psalms are prayers. They express every emotion in life: joy, sorrow, doubt, apathy, anger, fear, etc.</strong>  Reading
    the Psalms we find a profoundness in thought, understanding, and speech. The Psalmists have a way of speaking to God about their
    life I cannot match. 
</p>

<p>
    Dietrich Bonhoeffer explains the reason to pray the Psalms. The Bible, including the Psalms, is divinely inspired. This means
    each sentence contains the words of God written by the hands of men. <strong>With the Psalms, a book of prayers, God gave us a 
    divinely inspired book full of prayers to Himself!</strong>  The Psalms are essentially God-approved prayers. We have some specific
    examples from Jesus, especially the Lord&#39;s prayer, but then we have 150 more found in the Psalms!<br></p>

<p>
    <strong>It is easy to join with the Psalmists in prayer.</strong> Lets start with Psalm 37:4 - &quot;Oh taste and see that the Lord is good!&quot; We could respond, 
    &quot;Yes Father, my life clearly portrays your goodness. You took me when I was sad, lonely, and frightened, 
    freed me from my slavery to sin, and made me confident in You. Thank you for my salvation!
    Thank you for the way you show me your goodness in the people you have placed around me.&quot;
</p>
<p> 
    Continuing from v5 - &quot;Oh fear the Lord, you his saints, for those who fear him have no lack!&quot; We could respond, &quot;Increase my fear of you, Lord. 
    I depend on you for every need. You could take away all physical or mental abilities - even my life! - in an instant if you desired. 
    They all come from you. And even if my life takes a turn for the worse, and I lose everything, you will provide for my every need,
    just as you provided your Son to pay the penalty of death I earned for my rebellion. Please show your steadfast love to my friend
    who is struggling. Teach him to fear you as well, showing us both how in you we &#39;lack no good thing.&#39; &quot;
</p>

<p>
    It&#39;s as simple as that. As we follow along with the Psalm, we will be led to pray over areas of our life we
    might have completely forgotten otherwise. <strong>I am weak in the art of praising what I adore, so I have become
    an apprentice to the Psalmists, seeking their guidance.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Every book in the Bible can inspire prayer. Some places are easier than others,
    but we can always respond to the word of God in thankfulness or
    request, realigning our desires with His will.
</p>

<h3>Extra Benefits</h3>

<p>
    Praying the word not only deepens our communication with God, it deepens our understanding and love of His Word. <strong>As we spend time
    praying the scripture back to God, we are meditating on it and personalizing it.</strong>  We will not just read through the Bible, letting
    each verse fly over our head, but instead we are taking the time to let the word dig into our hearts and mind, pushing us to
    respond to God in what we say to him and what we do in our lives.
</p>

<p>
    To quote Don Whitney one more time:
</p>

<blockquote>
    <p>
        By this method, your prayers will be guided and shaped by Scripture, and be far more in conformity to the word and will of God than they will if you always make up your own prayers.
    </p>
</blockquote>

<h3>Conclusion</h3>

<p>
    As a disclaimer, praying the Bible is not a magic bullet to all our prayer needs, nor is it a requirement for
    every Christian. <strong>First and foremost we must learn how to be intimate with Christ.</strong>  We have to learn to devote time
    spent with Him, refreshing and nourishing our souls. <strong>Learning to have focused, intimate time with Christ is as important to
    our spiritual self as eating is to our physical.</strong>  What we do during that time, however, is not important as long as it
    is grounded in truth, which comes from the Bible. &quot;Sanctify them by the truth; Your word is truth.&quot; John 17:17.
</p>

<p>
    However, I definitely encourage you to give it a try yourself! <strong>For a trial run, take out time
    for the next few days to pray through a favorite Psalm each day, choosing a new one each time.</strong> If you don&#39;t have a favorite, 
    try out Psalm 1, 23, 34, 42, and 141. Simply read through the Psalm once to get a understanding of the text as a whole, then
    read a verse or phrase at a time, praying whatever comes to mind. If your mind wanders, go to the next verse or phrase!
</p>

<p>
    Have you ever done this method?  If not, do you think it could be helpful to you?  I would love to hear your thoughts on it
    as well as any other methods that may help people revitalize their prayer life!
</p>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/praying-scripture.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/praying-scripture.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 17:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Godliness is not a Means but an End]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<blockquote>
    <p>
        [He is] imagining that godliness is a means of gain. But godliness 
        with contentment is great gain, for we brought nothing into the world, 
        and we cannot take anything out of the world. - 1 Tim 6:5-7
    </p>
</blockquote>

<p>
    When previously I heard and read that verse, I
    never understood it.  When I considered the meaning, I would
    try to figure out what godliness gains.  Godliness gains much!
    For example, living a godly life brings joy in knowing we are pleasing the
    One we were made to please.  <strong>However, thinking just on that question
    misses the context of the passage.</strong>
</p>

<h3>An End, not a Means</h3>

<p>
    Looking before verse 6, we see Paul describing false teachers.
    These teachers use half-truths based on the gospel to sway
    the church members into following. This gains the teachers
    money, popularity, and power.  They avoid the
    <a href="offensive-gospel.html">offensive
    teachings of the gospel</a> and overexaggerate what people want to hear.
</p>

<p>
    If your gospel says, &quot;Follow Jesus, and you will have everything the
    world wants but keeps failing to get: money, power, success, health&quot;,
    take some time to consider your gospel; it&#39;s not the gospel
    Jesus brought.  The world is broken. <strong>Jesus
    did not come so that we could look like what the world glorifies.</strong> But
    we become the weak to shame the strong, the foolish to shame the wise, and those
    who are not to bring to nothing those that are (1 Cor 1:26-30).
</p>

<p>
    Paul here is saying that godliness is not a means to an end.  These false
    teachers are &quot;leading&quot; people to their own version of godliness, and this
    version glorifies the creation rather than the Creator.  <strong>The godliness
    that the people pursue is just a means to get some gain.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Paul corrects that thought.  Godliness is not a <em>means</em> of gain;
    godliness, with contentment, <em>is</em> great gain!  <strong>We should not be pursuing
    godliness so we can find our own personal gain, we should be pursuing 
    godliness as the gain.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Therefore trying to determine what gain godliness brings is completely
    missing the point.  Godliness <em>is</em> the great gain.
</p>

<h3>A Mindset Change</h3>

<p>
    Godliness, put simply, is the way our life pleases God. Paul says
    &quot;This is my aim, whether at home or away, to be pleasing to Him&quot; (2 Cor 5:10).
    We are made a new creation by faith in Jesus, and those who follow Him are
    loved and are made righteous, no longer to receive eternal wrath for disobedience.
    The love of God is unconditional and forever.
    But a parent can have unconditional love for a child
    and still at times receive great joy from the child and at others receive
    great grief.  <strong>Godliness is a lifestyle that brings our Father great
    joy.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    So how does living with the mindset of godliness
    being the end, being the great gain, affect my life?  It simplifies
    it!  We can look at everything as a means to the end of godliness.
    <strong>If godliness is truly our end, our great gain,
    we simply ask a question over every aspect of our life:
    &quot;Will this lead to godliness?&quot;</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Does my job lead to godliness?  How can I use this money to gain
    godliness?  I love my wife; how can I encourage her to gain godliness?
    My friend and I are going to hang out; what can I do or discuss
    in order to help us both gain godliness?  There is a stranger over there;
    can I do anything for him so that he can gain godliness?
</p>

<p>
    <strong>When seeing godliness as great gain, our time with Jesus becomes
    precious.</strong>  Time spent worshipping our Savior - reading
    and meditating on His Words, praying to Him, singing praise, etc -
    transforms us by the renewing of our mind to know
    the will of God: that which is good and acceptable and perfect 
    (Rom. 12:1-2).  That is godliness!  <strong>We go to Jesus, the only
    one who can satisfy our souls, to get godliness, the only end
    that is truly gain.</strong>
</p>

<h3>Conclusion</h3>

<p>
    I hope you see the beauty in pursuing godliness as an end rather than
    a means. <strong>Pursue with me and encourage others to pursue also.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Also, I would like to thank Sean Fuentes for a great Bible study that
    started this thought process and Clinton Fields for a helpful
    insights on it later.
</p>

<p>
    I&#39;d love to hear how you pursue godliness along with any other comments!
    Comment below, Facebook, or Twitter (@RTankersley).
</p>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/godliness-with-contentment.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/godliness-with-contentment.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 19:36:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Tech Reformation Podcast]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    Recently a few friends and I started up a podcast!  We have eight episodes currently
    released, and we are releasing a new episode every week!
</p>

<p>
    <strong>What is the podcast about? Where can you listen? How did we create it?</strong>
    If you are curious to know the answer to any of those, read on!
</p>

<h3>What is the Podcast About?</h3>

<p>
    The podcast is called <em>Tech Reformation</em>, with the tagline &quot;Where the world of technology meets the
    worldview of Christianity.&quot;  Four guys who love and follow Jesus and enjoy technology get together
    each week to merge the two together. 
</p>
<p>
    Technology is a huge part of our world today.  People are spending more time with electronics than
    ever before, new technologies are coming out every day, and many use them without thinking.
    We decided to think! <strong>We take the time to examine anything to do with technology,
    exploring the world&#39;s view and discussing the Christian&#39;s view.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    <strong>Also, anything that is a huge part of the culture is going to have a
    huge impact on our Kingdom work.</strong>  Some technology is built specifically for ministry,
    some technology is built for secular purposes but can be used for ministry, and some
    technology should be avoided altogether.  <strong>We look for ways we can best use technology
    for the glory of God.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    In the first segment, <strong><em>Tech You Should Know</em></strong>, we explore the week&#39;s technology news.
    Next up comes <strong><em>Tech You Should Use</em></strong> where we recommend a useful technology
    for your daily life. Finally, in <strong><em>Theology From the Headlines</em></strong>, we discuss current hot topics through the lens of
    a Christian worldview.
</p> 
<p>
    Currently we have discussed
    <ul>
        <li>Virtual, Augmented, and Mixed Reality</li>
        <li>Automating Jobs</li>
        <li>Smartphone Usage</li>
        <li>Drones</li>
        <li>Apple</li>
        <li>Free Internet</li>
        <li>Ad Blockers</li>
        <li>Internet Mob Justice</li>
    </ul>
</p>

<h3>Where Can I Listen?</h3>

<p>
    Interested in listening? <strong>The best place to start is our website at <a href="http://www.techreformation.com/">techreformation.com</a>!</strong> We post
    every episode to the site along with show notes containing links to the articles we discuss.
</p>

<p>
    Also, you can download a podcast app to your mobile device (I use <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bambuna.podcastaddict">Podcast Addict</a> on Android)
    and search &quot;Tech Reformation.&quot;  We&#39;re the only podcast that appears!  <strong>Most podcast apps allow you
    to download episodes so you can listen to them without Wi-Fi.</strong>
</p>

<h3>How Did it Start?</h3>

<p>
    It all started when a good friend of mine, Ben Robin, asked if I had any interest to do a podcast
    about technology and theology.  <strong>I enjoy both subjects, so I say I would be interested.</strong>  Time goes on, and he
    gets married and moves to Tennessee.  I forget about the podcast.
</p>

<p>
    A couple of weeks after the move, Ben sets up a meeting with me on Google Hangouts.  I expect he just wants to
    catch up since we haven&#39;t talked since his wedding.  <strong>You can imagine my surprise, then, when I
    realize two other guys I don&#39;t know will be joining the call, and we will be discussing the
    creation of a podcast!</strong>
</p>

<p>
    We have our first meeting where we just get to know each other a bit.  The two others are named
    Craig and Derek.  <strong>One fact is immediately apparent; Craig and Derek have never met. The only
    connection between us all is Ben.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    We converse for an hour, and then Ben has to leave.  Out of curiousity, I then
    ask Craig and Derek how they know Ben.  <strong>I learn that Ben tweeted, &quot;Anybody want to
    host a podcast with me?&quot;, and they were interested to join!</strong>  So, other than a few internet
    messages, they didn&#39;t know Ben either!
</p>

<p>
    <strong>Luckily, they are both awesome guys.</strong>  Over the next months, we slowly began preparing all the little
    details that need to be put into place, and on August 9th we released our first podcast!
</p>

<p>
    We have been recording every week since.  We have completed eight episodes and an introduction
    episode, and it has been a blast to create.  <strong>It&#39;s like hanging out with 3 friends to talk about
    Jesus for an hour, except we record it.</strong>
</p>

<h3>Conclusion</h3>

<p>
    If you like technology and/or love Jesus, check us out! I think you will enjoy it.
</p>

<p>
    Any podcasts that you enjoy listening to yourself?  I&#39;d be interested in hearing about them!
</p>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/tech-reformation.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/tech-reformation.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Day My Car Stopped Moving]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h3>More Car Problems</h3>
<p>
    <strong>The Tankersley family seems to be cursed with car troubles.</strong>  If that line sounds familiar, 
    <a href="http://blog.tankstudios.net/posts/broken-car.html">this post</a> started the same a month and a half ago.
</p>

<p>
    My cars just enjoy dying.  I&#39;ve never owned a new car, but I&#39;m not sure that would help. 
    Nobody knows when this curse came upon the family.  Maybe my great-grandpa didn&#39;t carry
    an old lady up a hill, and now I need to go to a juvenile camp and carry her great-grandson.  Maybe
    it&#39;s just confirmation bias.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>In any case, my car died again.</strong>  Here&#39;s the story of all the chaos that ensued; enjoy the ride!
</p>

<h3>Error in Transmission</h3>
<p>
    Every Friday morning, my church has prayer at 7:00AM.  One may think that is unreasonably early; however,
    Michelle and I have been waking up between 5:45 and 6:00 to run around the neighborhood.
    You may wonder, what are they running from?  We&#39;re running from calories! <strong>The more
    calories I burn, the more ice cream I can eat!</strong>
</p>
<p>
    Fridays are our short but hard days.  We run one mile as fast as we can!  This workout gives our legs diversity,
    but more importantly it gets us to prayer time on time.  After the run, we take our separate cars to the church.
    Roughly 2 minutes away, the excitement begins.  <strong>Speeding away from
    a stoplight going about 35 MPH, my car suddenly lurches!</strong>  Worriedly, I ask the car, &quot;Are you OK?&quot;  The car doesn&#39;t
    respond.  I continue to the church.
</p>
<p>
    Prayer time goes well, except when Sean notices that my front-passenger tire is flat.
    He always notices them flat; if he never looked at my car, the tires probably would never have issues.
    Maybe he&#39;s the one I need to carry up a hill...
</p>
<p>
    Planning to worry about the tire later, I head to work.  I get on the highway, but my car forcefully explains that
    getting on the highway is a terrible idea.  <strong>It does so by refusing to go above 35 MPH without revving up to
    5000 RPMs.</strong>  Not one to argue with my car, I immediately exit.  The car stays at 20 MPH...
    then 10...then stops moving.  It&#39;s acting like a stubborn dog that doesn&#39;t want to return home.  No matter
    how much gas I give it, it keeps its butt planted firmly on the ground.
</p>
<p>
    Working in an IT company, I&#39;ve learned the ultimate trick for fixing faulty hardware:  turn it
    off and back on.  Following this trick, my car decides it would love to drive more, and off we go!...
    at the crawling pace of 40MPH.  <strong>The poor thing just can&#39;t shift gears!</strong>  I decide to bring the car home rather than
    go straight to work, and, after one more incident of not being able to move, I make it home.
</p>

<h3>The Journey To Work</h3>
<p>
    I plan to just work at home for the day until I realize that, for the first time in two weeks, I
    left my computer at work.  Now I am at home with the perfect excuse to simply work at home for the day...and 
    I don&#39;t have my computer.  Being a software developer, a computer is pretty important.  <strong>Somehow I have
    to get to my office.</strong>
</p>
<p>
    So what do I do? <strong>I change into my running shoes and go for my second jog of the day!</strong> I have always believed that
    you never know when you are going to need the ability to run long distances.  Most days you don&#39;t. This day I do!
    My work is only 2 miles away from my house, and Michelle and I run that distance every day!
</p>
<p>
    We do not, however, run that distance in the heat.  It is now roughly 85 degrees outside.  We also typically
    shower before we are seen (or smelled) in public.  Running in the heat, in jeans, for 20 minutes,
    being a well-hydrated guy, I am definitely going to sweat.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>Today, I sweat a lot.</strong>
</p>
<h3>The Day At Work</h3>
<p>
    I enter my office as wet as if I had swam in my clothing.  Reaching my desk, I 
    suddenly realize how well the A/C works in the building.  InterWorks definitely accommodates the
    Northerners!  Realizing it is in everybody&#39;s best interest for me to not leave a puddle everywhere
    I go, I head to the bathroom to towel off.
</p>
<p>
    Then, the day of awesomeness begins.
</p>
<p>
    <strong>I walk into the kitchen and am met with breakfast food galore.</strong>  One person brought pastries from a bakery, one brought donuts from
    a donut shop, and one brought food from McDonalds.  Having just worked off a good number of calories, 
    I gave my body plenty of its most important nutrient: sugar.  Or high fructose corn syrup.
    <strong>Whatever it was, it was delicious.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    A short time later, I discover that InterWorks is bringing in lunch for the day!  Perfect timing, since I decided not to
    run with my lunch in hand.  <strong>I spend the lunch hour dining with friends on fluffy tacos.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    After lunch, I return to my office, exiting soon after upon hearing laughter in the hallway.  <strong>I uncover the source:
    my fellow coworkers are taking turns on a mini segue!</strong>
</p>

<img src="../img/immovable-car/erover.png" />

<p>
    I spend the next hour watching people riding and riding it myself.  These machines are awesome.  They appear
    impossible to use, but once you get the hang of it, they seem to follow your thoughts
    more than your feet.  <strong>They are brilliant little machines; try one out if you ever get the opportunity.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Finally, the day is over and Michelle picks me up.  I&#39;m definitely glad I left my computer at work.  <strong>I would have missed out
    on a great day otherwise!</strong>
</p>

<h3>The Cost</h3>

<p>
    Over the next week, Michelle and I attempt to get the car fixed.  First I bring it in to a Honda Dealer.  <strong>They want 
    to replace the transmission.</strong>  The cost: $5100 for used, $6300 for new.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>GULP</strong>
</p>

<p>
    I politely tell them my car is not worth that much, and I and retrieve it.  As I drive the car home, I wonder if this will be the last
    time I ever drive it.  Michelle and I attempt finding
    a better price.  After asking around, I find a shop that can do the repair for $3000.  <strong>We decide the price is good,
    and we bring the car in!</strong>
</p>

<p><h3>Conclusion</h3></p>
<p>
    <strong>The last time my car had issues, I shared how God often turns a bad situation into a good one.</strong><br>    Then, He took a situation that should have cost me $500 and made it nearly free, 
    <a href="http://blog.tankstudios.net/posts/offensive-gospel.html">then gave me the opportunity to share the gospel with the mechanic</a>!
</p>
<p>
    <strong>However, it does not always work out that way.</strong>  This instance is a prime example. I was left
    two weeks without a car and $3000 poorer. And what did I gain?  Well...at first glance, nothing.
</p>
<p>
    But what more do I need?  In Romans 8, Paul asks &quot;If God is for us, who can be against us?  He who did not spare His own
    Son but gave Him up for us all, how will He not also with Him graciously give us all things?&quot;  <strong>If God was willing
    to send Jesus as our replacement on the cross, what good is He going to withold?  He has already given us the
    greatest gift ever; there&#39;s nothing left to withhold!</strong>
</p>
<p>
    But how does that make sense in this case?  He withheld the good of a fixed car 
    that doesn&#39;t cost $3000, right?  <strong>Sure, if we consider
    a car and money as the most important!</strong>  But Paul says 
</p>

<blockquote>
    For Christ&#39;s sake I have suffered the loss of all things
    and count them as rubbish, in order that I may gain Christ and be found in Him, not having a righteousness of my own
    that comes from the law, but that which comes through faith in Christ, the righteousness from God that depends on faith, that
    I may know Him and the power of His resurrection, and may share in His sufferings, becoming like Him in His death, that by any
    means possible I may attain the ressurection from the dead. - Phil 3:8-10
</blockquote>

<p>
    <strong>The greatest gift that God ever gave is Jesus!  And the great gift that He continually gives us is Jesus.</strong>  The &quot;loss&quot; of my
    car and money really mean nothing to me.  Jesus will never leave me nor forsake me (Heb 13:8).  What can I 
    possibly lose?  And if somehow being without a car for two weeks and being out $3000 lets me know Him even more?  <strong>Then
    I count the car and money as rubbish.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Life won&#39;t be easy.  Above, Paul specifically says that to know Christ&#39;s resurrection we must share in His sufferings. Christ
    suffered far greater than we ever can, but we will have our own sufferings.  However, suffering never means God is withholding
    good, because God is never withholding the righteousness that comes from Jesus and the joy of knowing Him!
    <strong>If you are suffering, let it draw you deeper into your Savior.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    Thank you for reading!  Come back next month for another dead car story!  Thoughts, questions, stories, whatever?  Comment
    below or on Facebook!
</p>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/immovable-car.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/immovable-car.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 14:43:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jesus in the OT - Jesus the Snake]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
    We would never compare Jesus to a snake.  Why would we? The snake is forever remembered as the enemy - the tempter who led Eve to take the first bite of the forbidden fruit.
    Jesus is the offspring in Genesis 3 who crushes the head of the snake! <strong>Whoever makes that comparison must be crazy...</strong>
</p>

<p>
    <strong>But that would mean Jesus is crazy.</strong>  John 3:16 is perhaps the most well-known verse: &quot;For God so loved the world, that He gave His only Son,
    that whoever believes in Him should not perish but have eternal life.&quot;  But notice, the first word in that sentence is &quot;For.&quot;
    The word &quot;for&quot; means something preceded that statement.  So let&#39;s take a step back:
</p>

<blockquote>
    <p>
        No one has ascended into heaven except He who descended from Heaven, the Son of Man.  And as Moses lifted up the serpent in the wilderness, so must
        the Son of Man be lifted up, that whoever believes in Him may have eternal life. - John 3:13-15.
    </p>
</blockquote>

<p>
    See, Jesus compares Himself to a serpent!  In memory of <a style="color: cornflowerblue;" title="The Offensive Gospel" href="/posts/snake-attack.html">my near death by snake</a>, this section of JOT (Jesus in the Old Testament) will
    explain why Jesus calls Himself a snake.  You can read the intro to the JOT series <a style="color: cornflowerblue;" title="JOT Intro" href="/posts/jot-intro.html">here</a>.
</p>

<h3>The Grumbling Israelites</h3>

<p>
    <strong>Let&#39;s first step back from Jesus&#39; time.</strong>  A big step...all the way back to Moses.  Moses is leading the nation of Israel around in circles in the wilderness.
    Moses got them to the Promised Land, but the nation freaked out because the people were giant!  Not trusting God, they went back into the wilderness; having
    just escaped slavery in Egypt, there was nowhere for them to go.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>These people have seen God do incredible things time and time again.</strong>  They follow a giant pillar of dust by day and fire by night! Bread falls from the sky,
    water comes from a rock, the ground has opened under men, and so much more.  Yet once again, the Israelites complain about God to Moses: &quot;Why have you brought us up out of Egypt
    to die in the wilderness? For there is no food and no water, and we loathe this worthless food!&quot; (Num. 21:5)
</p>

<p>
    They are like the entire human race.  Our very existence relies on God&#39;s will (Rev 4:11).  We see and hear of His acts, but we rebel. We hate Him,
    we ignore Him, and we mock Him. We use the name of our Creator as a curse!  <strong>We, like the Israelites here,
    declare that all the good He does is evil.</strong>  In this world, treason against your nation is considered a terrible crime, but <strong>we have been
    committing treason against The Divine from the beginning.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    God, being just, declares the sentence for their crime: &quot;Then the Lord sent fiery serpents among the people, and they bit the people, so that many people of Israel died.&quot;
    However, immediately following, the people come to Moses saying &quot;We have sinned, for we have spoken against the Lord and you.  Pray to the Lord, that He take
    away the serpents for us.&quot; And Moses prays, and the Lord, as merciful as He is just, provides a way for them to be healed: &quot;Make a fiery serpent and set it on
    a pole, and everyone who is bitten, when he sees it, shall live.&quot;  <strong>Moses obeys, and the people who look at the serpent on the pole live.</strong> (Num. 21:6-9)
</p>

<h3>Jesus the Serpent</h3>

<p>
    Now lets return to John 3:14-16.  In this passage, Jesus is talking to a man named Nicodemus. Nicodemus wanted to speak to Jesus because he believed it was
    clear that Jesus came from God.  They then get into a discussion about entering the Kingdom of Heaven, during which
    Jesus explains, &quot;As Moses lifted up the serpent in the wilderness, so must the Son of Man be lifted up, that whoever believes in Him
    may have eternal life.&quot;
</p>

<p>
    Nicodemus is a Pharisee - a member of the religious elite.  He knows the book of Numbers better than anyone else.  The full story of the Israelites
    would have flashed through Nicodemus&#39; head when Jesus spoke of the serpent in the wilderness.
    Now that we have the information Nicodemus had, let&#39;s look at what Jesus was saying.<br></p>

<p>
    The people of Israel had rebelled against God, declaring the good He does as bad.
    We, likewise, do the same every day.  This evil deserves punishment. We have earned the cup of God&#39;s wrath on the Day of Judgment.
    We have already committed this crime.  <strong>No good we do now can cover our sin, just as a murderer cannot clear his name by being good the rest of his life.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    <strong>But God, being merciful, provided a way to be free of this judgment.</strong>  First we must recognize our sin against God, as the Israelites did.  We must believe that
    we are rebels, completely deserving our punishment and completely hopeless to avert it.  <strong>God graciously provides a Substitute, the snake, Jesus, and sets Him on a pole, the cross.
    And if we look to the snake on the pole, Jesus on the cross, we will be saved!</strong>  The venom in us, the sin in us, means certain, eternal death (Rom. 6:23). We are dead men walking. But
    when we look upon the snake, Jesus on the cross, we will be brought back to life!
</p>

<p>
    The snake - the lying, deceitful snake that led us away from God in the beginning - is our father.  Jesus tells the general Jewish populace, &quot;You are of your father the devil, and your
    will is to do your father&#39;s desire.&quot;  Jesus saves us by becoming the snake as well.  <strong>While on the cross, all the acts of rebellion we commit against God are placed upon Jesus!</strong>
</p>

<blockquote>
    <p>
        [Jesus] was pierced for our transgressions; He was crushed for our iniquities; upon Him was the chastisement
        that brought us peace, and with His wounds...we are healed.  We all like sheep have gone astray; we have turned - every one - to his own way; and the Lord
        has laid on Him the iniquity of us all (Is. 53:5-6).
    </p>
</blockquote>

<h3>Conclusion</h3>

<p>
    Wow...just wow.  If that does not leave you in speechless awe of our Lord and Savior, I do not know what will.  Just as God raised up a snake on a pole when the Israelites
    sinned in the time of Moses, the Son of Man must be lifted up on the cross, so that any who believe will be saved from their sin and have eternal life.  For God so loved the world that He gave His only Son,
    the Son who knew no sin but became sin, became the snake, for us all, so that whoever believes in Him will have eternal life, becoming the righteousness of God in Him (Jn. 3:14-15, 2 Cor. 5:21).
</p>

<p>
    <strong>John 3:16 grows in depth and power when we see how the OT created the same picture hundreds of years before.</strong>  I hope this post has grown your love of
    John 3:16, the OT, and most importantly, Jesus.  If you have never looked to the snake on the pole, please do!  The venom is sliding through your body, leaving
    you a dead man walking, and you will be sentenced to death on the Day of Judgment.  Our only hope is letting Jesus endure the punishment for us.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>Thank you for reading!</strong>  I would love any feedback in the comments below, Twitter (@RTankersley), Facebook, or in person if you can find me!
</p>

<p>
    See you next time!
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/jot-snake.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/jot-snake.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 16:52:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>