<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Tank Studios]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Blogging about my walk with Jesus in a modern world]]></description>
        <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net/</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:45:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://blog.tankstudios.net//rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:45:39 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jesus in the Old Testament - Introduction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/jot/book.jpg" style="display: none;" /></p>
<p>
    The Old Testament (OT) is an interesting set of books.  I can safely assume most Christians have not read the OT entirely, and
    I can definitely assume most Christians know and understand the New Testament (NT) better than the OT. I am among the latter group.
    And finally, some Christians, likely only find benefit in that it adds weight to the hardcover book, letting it be a holy paperweight 
    and gaining arm strength lugging it around.
</p>

<p>
    <strong>However, there is an amazing depth in the OT when read understanding its purpose.  I hope to explain that purpose, and in each further post in this series, explain
    an OT story, showing how that story meets the purpose.</strong>
</p>

<p><h3>What is the OT?</h3></p>
<p>
    Before delving into the purpose, let us briefly discuss what the OT is.  <strong>The OT is a series of books outlining the history of the Jewish nation and their interaction with God.</strong>
    There are several different series that were written in similar ways with a similar mindset.  The series are as follows<br></p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Books of the Law</strong> - Tells the story of creation, shows God choosing the Israelites, details them reaching the land He promises them (modern day Israel), and lists out
    the laws God gives them to follow, such as the Ten Commandments.</li>
    <li><strong>Books of History</strong> - Tells the story of the Israelites taking over the Promised Land and their ups and downs in following the laws of God up through around 400 B.C.</li>
    <li><strong>Books of Wisdom</strong> - Explains life proverbs, discusses the meaning of life, and contains prayers and songs of individuals to God.</li>
    <li><strong>Major Prophets</strong> -  Contains the words of God spoken through men to Israel, rebuking, foretelling judgement, and promising restoration after repentance.</li>
    <li><strong>Minor Prophets</strong> - Contains the same as above, but in (typically) shorter books.</li>
</ul>

<p><h3>What did the Jewish Nation Believe of the OT?</h3></p>
<p>
    Knowing what the OT contains, lets talk about why it was written.  <strong>Paul says that all Scripture is God-breathed and useful (1 Tim. 3:16-17).</strong>
    In Jesus&#39; time, the Jews held the OT in high esteem.  They strictly followed the laws and sacrifices
    listed in the book of the Law.  The sang the Psalms and searched out the meanings of the prophets.  <strong>They believed their salvation into eternal life
    rested within the scriptures.</strong>
</p>

<p><h3>Jesus&#39; Explanation of OT&#39;s Purpose</h3></p>
<p>
    And they were correct!  But many did not understand how it led to eternal life.    <strong>Jesus Himself calls them out and explains
    that they have completely missed the purpose.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    In John 5, the Pharisees -- the Jew&#39;s religious leaders -- come asking Jesus who testifies with Him that
    He is the Christ.  Jesus tells them that John the Baptist testifies (Jn 1:29), Jesus&#39; works of the Father testify (...all 4 gospels), and finally that the entire OT testifies:
</p>

<p><div></p>
<p><blockquote style="font-style: italic;">
    You search the Scriptures because you think that in them you have eternal life; and it is they that bear witness about me, yet you refuse to come to me that you may have life...
    Do not think that I will accuse you to the Father.  There is one who accuses you: Moses, on whom you have set your hope.  For if you believed Moses, you would believe
    Me; for He wrote of me. (Jn 5:38-46)
</blockquote>
</div></p>
<p>
    The Pharisees knew entire OT in and out, but when Jesus came, they rejected Him!  <strong>Jesus tells them that if they truly believed what they were reading,
    they would not be rejecting Jesus; they would be worshipping Him!</strong>
</p>

<p>
    <strong>So we see, the OT does point to eternal life because in its entirety -- every single letter -- it points to Jesus.</strong>  It details how we fall short of the glory of God,
    fail in our role as His image bearers, and desperately need a Savior.  It explains that from our failures we have earned the wrath of God, and that just
    as a murderer has to pay the penalty for breaking the law, we also must pay the penalty for rebelling against our Creator.  And finally, it points to the One
    who will come to save us; He will come, bear the wrath of God in our place, give us the chance to have His right standing before God, and reign as Lord over all.
    For a fuller picture of this, please read <a style="color: cornflowerblue;" title="The Offensive Gospel" href="/posts/offensive-gospel.html">this explanation
    of the Gospel from Romans 5</a>.
</p>

<p><h3>Conclusion</h3></p>
<p>
    I hope this post has excited you to see all the ways the OT points to Jesus.  <strong>Understanding this concept has deepened my love for the OT, and it always excites me
    when I find in it another picture of what Christ has done for us.</strong>  God always comes up with the best symbolism and parables.
</p>

<p>
    I would enjoy hearing about your love for the OT! Comment below or on Facebook to give your feedback! 
</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/jot-intro.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/jot-intro.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:44:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Gospel is Offensive]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/offensive-gospel/divide.jpg" style="display: none;" /></p>
<p>
    Recently I told a <a style="color: cornflowerblue;" title="The Day My Car Panicked" href="/posts/broken-car.html">story about my car getting fixed</a>.  During that time, I shared the gospel with the mechanic.
    The mechanic told me he has no interest in following Jesus.  He does not even believe Jesus
    walked the Earth!  <strong>However, he explained that he enjoys hearing messages from a well-known preacher.</strong>
</p>

<p>
    His explanation confused me.  <strong>What about the gospel could a person
    who completely rejects the Godhood and Lordship of Christ enjoy?</strong>  The only explanation is that pastor
    must have not preached the gospel.
</p>

<p><h3>The Offenses</h3></p>
<p>
    Paul claims that in sharing the knowledge of Christ, &quot;we are the aroma of Christ in God both to those who are being saved
    and those who are perishing. To one a fragrance from death to death, to the other a fragrance from life to life.&quot; 2 Cor. 2:16.
    <strong>When we explain the gospel of Christ, we share the gospel in love, but people will not always love the gospel.</strong>
    Please join me in Romans 5:6-11 as I explain why.
</p>

<p><h4>We Exist because God Allows It</h4></p>
<p>
    &quot;For while we were still weak, at the right time, Christ died for the ungodly.&quot; Rom. 5:6.
</p>
<p>
    We want to be independent, but the gospel explains that we are weak.
    <strong>In fact, Rev 4:11 says we would stop existing if Jesus stopped wanting us to exist.</strong>
    Jesus could also stop our heart from beating or stop giving us air to breath.
    The gospel offends our pride in our independency.
</p>
<h4>We have Rebelled</h4>
<p>
    &quot;God shows His love for us in that while we were still sinners, Christ died for us.&quot; Rom 5:8.
</p>
<p>
    We want to be blameless, but the gospel explains that we have broken God&#39;s law.
    <strong>We are &quot;by nature children of wrath&quot; (Eph 2:3). There is no one good, not even one (Ps. 14:3).</strong>
    The gospel offends our self-righteousness.
</p>
<h4>We will be Condemned</h4>
<p>
    &quot;Since therefore we have been justified by His blood, much more shall we be saved by Him from
    the wrath of God.&quot; Rom. 5:9.
</p>
<p>
    We want to be free of responsibility, but the gospel explains that
    we will be condemned for our rebellion against our Creator.  Murdering only once
    brands us as a murderer, deserving punishment.  Breaking God&#39;s law (sinning) only once brands us a sinner, and
    we have all sinned and fallen short of the glory of God (Rom 3:23).  God is just, vengeance is His, He will repay (Deut 32:35).
    <strong>Justice will be served, evil will be destroyed, and God accomplishes this at judgement, condemning
    sinners to an eternity in hell.</strong>
    The gospel offends our desire to be free of responsibility for our evil.
</p>
<h4>We Cannot Save Ourselves</h4>
<p>
    &quot;For if while we were enemies we were reconciled to God by the death of His Son, much more, now that
    we are reconciled, shall we be saved by His life.&quot; Rom 5:10.
</p>

<p>
    We want to be good enough on our own, but the gospel explains, as stated earlier, that
    we have all sinned and will have God&#39;s wrath poured out on us. We can do
    nothing to prevent that.  But Jesus did!  While we were DEAD in our sins, we were saved by grace
    through faith in Jesus Christ, not by works so that none may boast (Eph 2:8).  Praise Jesus for doing
    what none of us could do!  He lived a perfect life, and
    God made Him who knew no sin to be sin on our behalf so that in Him
    we might become the righteousness of God (2 Cor 5:21)!  <strong>By believing in Jesus we are legally made
    not guilty in the sight of God!</strong>
    The gospel offends our confidence in ourselves.
</p>
<h4>We Must Follow Jesus as Lord</h4>
<p>
    &quot;More than that, we also rejoice in God through our Lord Jesus Christ, through whom we have now received
    reconciliation.&quot; Rom 5:11.
</p>

<p>
    We do not want to submit to anyone; we want to live a life where we simply eat, drink, and be merry (1 Cor 15:32), but the
    gospel explains that Jesus, being God in flesh
    (1 Tim. 3:16), demands our obedience.  Truly believing in Him requires us to accept Him as Lord of our life.
    We are made a new creation (2 Cor 5:17), our sin is crucified with Him on the cross, we are buried with Him in death, and we
    are risen to walk with Him in His resurrection to life (Rom 6:4).  <strong>Living lives our own way shows we have no love
    for Him and that we have never been justified and made new.</strong>  The gospel offends our authority over ourselves.
</p>

<p><h3>Conclusion - Jesus is Life</h3></p>
<p>
    I hope you see how this message is offensive to those who do not believe.  <strong>If there is no love for Jesus,
    nobody can find any of the above to be the &quot;good news&quot; believers know it to be.  When we as believers
    preach the gospel, we must preach it this way. Any other message will not save.</strong>  The gospel is the power
    of God for salvation to those who believe (Rom 1:16), but if someone comes with a different gospel,
    they will be accursed (Gal 1:8).
</p>

<p>
    If you do not follow Jesus as Lord, <strong>I BEG you on behalf of Jesus Christ, be reconciled to God!</strong>
    God made Him who knew no sin to be sin on YOUR behalf so that in Jesus you might become the
    righteousness of God (2 Cor 5:20-21).  Please believe.  Jesus came that we may have life and life in
    abundance (Jn 10:10).  He is the best master to have.  Go to Him, for He gives rest,
    His yoke is easy, and His burden is light (Matt 11:28-30).
</p>

<p>
    Thank you for reading.  I welcome any feedback.<br></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/offensive-gospel.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/offensive-gospel.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Day My Car Panicked]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/broken-car/old-car.jpg" style="display: none;" /></p>
<h3>Car Problems</h3>
<p><strong>The Tankersley family seems to be cursed with car troubles.</strong>  to the extent a man wanted to write a book 
about our many difficulties. Discovering my car has another 
problem is like waking up to a shiny, new pimple on my face.  It is common enough to not be
surprising, but I wish I could just make it go away for good.</p>

<p><strong>Recently, a metaphorical pimple manifested in a most inconvenient way.</strong></p>

<h3>Locked Door</h3>
<p><strong>My car door lock had been finicky.  It was refusing to accept my key as the proper key.</strong>  I always managed to unlock the car, but
eventually I took it into a Honda dealer.  They fixed it...for a week.  But it once again began to be finicky.</p>

<p>I decided to stop locking my front car door.  I would every other door, just not the front.  My car helped me accomplish this plan
in that the automatic lock would lock all but the front door.</p>

<p><strong>Or so I thought...</strong></p>

<p>Pulling up to my office, I get out of the car and close the door.  Remembering I need to lock all but the
front door, I open the door again, hit the lock button, and let gravity close the door for me.</p>

<p>As it shuts, I suddenly realize that my car has betrayed me; <strong>it locked all 4 doors!</strong>  I attempt
to stick my fingers in the door before gravity finishes the dirty deed, but I am left only with a jammed finger
and the bitter taste of defeat.<p>

<p>I decide to deal with it later, but as I walk towards my office, I realize my phone is still in the car.
Not sure how long I have until phone withdrawal kicks in, I turn around and spend the next fifteen minutes,
key in the door, twisting, jamming, and begging.  <strong>Finally, I head into my office with no success.</strong></p>

<p>My wife is kind enough to pick me up at the end of the day.  We try her key to no avail.  I plan to try
again the next day.  If I cannot get the key into the door, I will call a person to pop the lock open for
me and then bring the car back to the dealership.</p>

<h3>Pop-A-Lock</h3>

<p><strong>At lunch the next day, I head to my car in prayer.</strong>  &quot;Father, it would be wonderful if You opened this door
for me.  I know You can.  It would save me $50 and the headache of having people come out
to open it.  So why not?  This is my attempt, and then I will call roadside service.
I trust Your plan and will.&quot;</p>

<p>Expecting a miracle, I continue jiggling the key, again to no avail.  <strong>Dejected, I call the Pop-A-Lock guy.</strong>
He comes and pops the lock open in roughly 30 seconds, completely shaking my confidence
that my locked car is actually safe.  <strong>I then open the door...and the car enters panic mode</strong>.</p>

<p>The security alarm honks constantly if the car is not unlocked properly, which I had no way to do!
The horn dies down after about 5 minutes, but
reopening a door or starting the ignition causes it to flare up all over again.  We set the alarm off
three times trying to solve the problem.  I am now the favorite person of all the businesses in the area.</p>

<p>The Pop-A-Lock man gives up, but he tells me he will wave the $45 fee of opening the door and
send a new guy out to replace my entire lock!  Thanking him, I turn to go inside...until I once again realize
my phone is still in the car.  I prepare myself for the hatred of all around me, open the door, grab my phone,
and walk away as my car repeatedly cries out its panicked alarm.<p>

<h3>The Repair</h3>
<p>A few hours later, a man comes to repair the door.  As he is repairing the door, we chat for about an hour.
<strong>In that time, I get to tell him about following Jesus, and I invite him to my church!</strong></p> 

<p>Once he fixes the lock, I ask about getting a remote key for keyless entry.  I learn I can at no extra cost!
For $130, a man comes to pop my lock, then another comes to replace my lock, and finally they make a third
trip to give me a remote entry key!  A dealership would price that around $300. <strong>If God had answered
my request to have the door opened, I would have paid way more money, I would have been without
a car for a few days, and I wouldn&#39;t have gotten to share the gospel.</strong>  I&#39;m glad God followed His plan rather
than answering my request in the way I asked.</p>

<p><h3>Conclusion</h3></p>
<p> In Philippians, Paul tells us to be anxious for nothing, but instead make our requests to God, and 
His peace that surpasses all understanding will guard our hearts.  Sometimes we see God work things out in an awesome way.
Sometimes we are left wondering why God didn&#39;t answer our request
the way we expected Him to answer.</p>

<p><strong>Paul doesn&#39;t tell us God will answer how we want.</strong>  Paul simply explains
we can have peace knowing that God has heard our request and will work all things together for good to
those who love Him and are called according to His purpose.  <strong>Obediently trusting Him with our requests will
give us peace and lead us closer to Jesus, and Jesus is worth more than time, money, and any
other created thing.</strong></p>

<p>So today, determine what is making you anxious, make your request to God, and trust that He
will work it out in a way that leads the most people to His Son.  <strong>If knowing Jesus more isn&#39;t an
appealing result, please seek to understand how Christians can say, &quot;I count all things as rubbish compared
to the joy of knowing Christ Jesus my Lord.&quot;</strong></p>

<p>I hope you enjoyed the story!  I look forward to any feedback, questions, or stories that you have to give!
Comment with them below</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/broken-car.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/broken-car.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:44:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing Your Life Projects and To-Do Lists with Trello]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/trello/writing.jpg" style="display: none;" /></p>
<p>Most of us have so many tasks to do we lose track of them all. We may make lists, but we often need the list when we don&#39;t have it, or we simply let it fall out of date.
<strong>Trello provides a free, easy way to create and manage tasks from wherever you are</strong>.</p>

<p><img src="/img/trello/trello.PNG" alt="Trello Logo"></p>

<p>I have been using Trello for half a year now and have found it to be beneficial to practical life management.  Here is how.</p>

<h3>Trello: The Answer to Task Management Woes</h3>

<p><a title="Trello" href="http://www.trello.com/">Trello</a> allows you to manage tasks in a simple, stylish, and effective way. 
<strong>Trello can revolutionize your task lists in three ways: categorizing, detailing, and syncing</strong>.</p>

<p><h3>Categorizing</h3></p>
<p>On a paper task list, there are typically two categories: to-do and done.  Trello allows three levels of categorization.</p>

<p><h4>Boards</h4></p>
<p>First, similar tasks are categorized into Boards.  Boards are the highest level.  One board may contian all the tasks for the house.  Another board may contain all the tasks for the office.
<strong>Boards give clear distinctions between contexts</strong>.</p>

<p><img src="/img/trello/trelloboards.PNG" alt="Trello Boards"></p>

<p><h4>Lists</h4></p>
<p><strong>Second, tasks within the context of a board, are grouped into lists</strong>.  These lists allow you to further organize tasks.  Want to be able to measure the progress of a task?  Then perhaps
you would organize your boards into progress lists, &quot;Not Started&quot;, &quot;In Progress&quot;, &quot;Almost There&quot;, and &quot;Done&quot;.  Would you rather, instead
further narrow down the context of your boards?  Your lists could then be, &quot;Kitchen&quot;, &quot;Garage&quot;, &quot;Living Room&quot;, and &quot;Bathroom&quot;.</p>

<p><img src="/img/trello/list.PNG" alt="Trello Lists"></p>

<p>But what if you want to measure both progress and context?  Labels solve that problem.</p>

<p><h4>Labels</h4></p>
<p>Finally, tasks can be attached with labels.  <strong>Tasks can have as many labels attached as
desired</strong>.  So, a red label could mean &quot;Not Started&quot;, a yellow label could mean &quot;In progress&quot;, and
a green label could mean &quot;done&quot;.</p>

<p><img src="/img/trello/listwithlabels.PNG" alt="List With Labels"></p>

<p>Alternatively, a red label could mean &quot;Kitchen&quot;, yellow &quot;Garage&quot;, green &quot;Living Room&quot;, and blue &quot;Bathroom&quot;.</p>

<p>All these categories can be used in whatever way you want!  Nearly all of my boards are categorized differently to suit my needs.</p>

<p><h3>Detailing</h3></p>
<p>With traditional pen and paper tasklists, there is not much room for details.  With too many details, the paper will get cluttered, and it will no longer be simple and succinct.
<strong>With Trello, you can get a clean tasklist when you only want an overview, but you then can get detailed tasks on further examination</strong>.</p>

<p>When looking at a Trello board, you can see details about a task at a glance.  You can see the list it
is on, the labels it has attached,
the due date you have set, and the people the task is assigned to.  These details are all added
elegantly so they only draw your eye when you are looking for them.</p>

<p><img src="/img/trello/complexlist.PNG" alt="Complex List"></p>

<p>When you click a task, you get the opportunity to see and add even more details!  Inside the task editor, tasks can receive checklists, images, comments, and a variety of other details.</p>

<p><h3>Syncing</h3></p>
<p>If you own a smartphone, your tasks are always on-hand.  Trello is a web-based application with apps on all smartphones.  <strong>Using Trello, 
you no longer have to carry a tasklist around with you</strong>.</p>

<p>Also, if there is a group of people you want working with you on the taskboard, members can be added to the board.  <strong>If one person changes a task, all members of the board immediately get the changes</strong>!</p>

<p><h3>Conclusion</h3></p>
<p>Trello has been a huge help to my wife and I in managing house and life projects.  <strong>What do you think?  Worth trying out, or do you already have a method you are happy with?</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/trello.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/trello.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plastic for Dinner]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="/img/plastic-for-dinner/stove.jpg" style="display: none;" /></p>
<p><h3>Bad Planning</h3></p>
<p><strong>I am not a chef</strong>.  I belive good chefs are artists. <strong>Good chefs know how to improvise.  I do not.</strong></p>

<p>My lovely wife does most of the cooking.  Everything she makes is delicious.  She has the ability to improvise.</p>

<p>This day, she was not arriving at the house until 6:15, and we had somewhere to be at 7:00, <strong>meaning it is my turn to cook.</strong>
I have roughly 7 meals I can make edible.  My planned dish for the evening: honey salsa chicken.</p>

<p><img class="small-image" src="/img/plastic-for-dinner/stove.jpg" alt="Open Stove"></p>

<p>I arrive home at 5:45 and begin preparing the ingredients.  With the ingredients prepared, I read the directions.
The final step: bake for one hour.</p>

<p><h3>Improvisation</h3></p>
<p>Dinner would be <em>ready</em> at 7:00.  <strong>Baking for an hour wouldn&#39;t
even give me time to finish it, much less eat it!</strong></p>

<p>Remember said inability to improvise?  I pull everything I have out of my improvisation skill
bucket and come up with a brilliant idea!</p>

<p>I call my wife.</p>

<p>...voicemail: &quot;Hi, this is Michelle Tankersley.&quot;</p>

<p>Having already used all my improvisation for the day, I am trapped with my idea.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Call</strong>: &quot;Hi, this is Michelle Tankersley.&quot;</li>
<li><strong>Call</strong>: &quot;Hi, this is Michelle Tankersley.&quot;</li>
<li><strong>Call</strong>: &quot;Hi, this is Michelle Tankersley.&quot;</li>
<li><strong>Call</strong>: &quot;Hi, this is Michelle Tankersley.&quot;</li>
</ul>

<p>After five back-to-back calls, I decide she must not be picking up.  However, being determined to provide my wife with honey salsa chicken, 
I drink the dregs of my remaining improvisation, and, <strong>for the first time in my cooking history, I develop a plan!</strong></p>
<p><h3>Spilling the Nachos</h3>
&quot;I can cook it in a skillet!&quot;  Using a skillet on a stove top is much faster than baking, and it would get the job done!</p>
<p><img class="small-image" src="/img/plastic-for-dinner/stovetop.jpg" alt="Stovetop"></p>

<p>Being pleased with the idea, I rush to begin.  My enthusiasm quickly fades when I see the pan of leftover nachos from the night before, enjoying its place on our best working stove top.
<strong>As I pick it up to pour the crumbs into the trash, my phone rings.</strong></p>
<p>In a desire to get to the phone before I missed the call, <strong>I quickly scrape off the nachos...all over the floor.</strong>  &quot;No time!&quot; I think, throwing the nacho pan into the sink.
Before sprinting into the living room, I turn on the burner to let it warm.  I race to the living room, grab the phone, move my thumb to answer...and the ringing ends.</p>
<p>Seconds away.  Love it when that happens.</p>
<p><h3>Plastic Fumes</h3>
The call was from Michelle.  I call her back and this time she answers.  We have a chat about my idea, and she agrees I should continue with the plan.  Again excited
to create my delicious chicken, <strong>I return to the kitchen, only to find my cat, Tessie, enjoying a second dinner consisting of nacho crumbs.</strong>
Shooing her away, I get the broom out of the closet, toss the dust pan to the side, and begin furiously sweeping up the crumbs.</p>
<p>Finished, I look around for the dustpan.  My eyes land on it.  <strong>When tossing the dustpan to the side, it managed to settle right on top of the burner!</strong></p>
<p>Immediately pulling the dustpan off, I discover a nice hole burned through it, leaving behind a puddle of melted plastic still cooking on the burner.  Still, the dustpan works well enough to sweep up the nacho crumbs.</p>
<p><img class="small-image" src="/img/plastic-for-dinner/dustpan.jpg" alt="Burnt Dustpan"></p>

<p>The burning plastic is filling the air above the stove with smoke.  The air smelled just like cancer.  Delicious.</p>
<p><h3>Enjoying the Meal</h3>
I scrape the plastic off the burner with a grill cleaner and begin cooking the chicken.  Michelle returns home, and she is thankfully forgiving of my attempt to destroy everything we own.
<strong>The chicken finishes, we enjoy a nice, home-cooked meal, and we arrive at our destination at 7:05.  Victory!</strong></p>
<p><h3>Conclusion</h3>
We can&#39;t all be good cooks, and we don&#39;t all get to enjoy the smell of burning plastic, but we all know the sweet feeling of victory after countless defeats.
I thank God for reminding me of Phillipians 2:14 in the middle of this experience: &quot;Do all things without grumbling and arguing&quot;. Holding His Word in front of me, I stayed humored rather than annoyed.
I hope He continues working in me so that when life gets much messier than spilled nachos and burnt dust pans, <strong>I will find joy in knowing Jesus
as Savior and Lord, joy in what He did on the cross, and all trials will be nothing in the light of His saving grace.  That is &quot;life, and life in abundance.&quot;</strong></p>
<p>I hope you enjoyed my story!  Any feedback or similar moments that you have to share?  Leave a comment!</p>
]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/plastic-for-dinner.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/plastic-for-dinner.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:45:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Post!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello everybody!  Thank you for coming to Tank Studios Blog.  My name is Ryan Tankersley 
and I&#39;ll be the author of these posts.  Feel free to check out the <a title="About Page" href="blog.tankstudios.net/about.html">About Page</a> to see what I&#39;m all about.</p>
<h3>Wait, Haven&#39;t You Done This Before?</h3>

<p>...Yeah.  The first one, Tank Studios Tech Talk, was a primer to see if I enjoyed blogging.  <strong>I did, but I felt limited</strong>. 
First, the blog never felt like mine.  I&#39;m a software developer.  I wanted the site to be mine in the sense that I knew the code.  Blogger gave me 
a nice, pre-packaged template that I liked, but again, it never felt like mine.  I made this website using <a title="DocPad" href="http://www.docpad.org/">DocPad</a>.
DocPad makes creating websites with Html, JavaScript, and CSS much easier than simply starting from scratch, and I can change anything on this site
that I want to.</p>
<p>Secondly, I desired a broader scope than just Tech Talk.  <strong>Here I will be discussing three core subjects: Life, Tech, and Dev</strong>.
Each subject will be tagged appropriately, so if a person only care about Life posts, that person can check the &quot;Life&quot; tag for all relevant posts.</p>
<p>Please allow me to explain each tag.</p>
<h4>Life</h4>

<p>The Life tag will be stories from my life.  I follow Jesus as Lord, and I love discussing what that looks like.  Many Life posts will be theological.
I also enjoy funny stories and would like to share entertaining experiences as they come.  <strong>I hope to allow people to walk through my life and
give glory to God through my thoughts, encouragements, and stories</strong>.</p>
<h4>Tech</h4>

<p>If you read much of Tank Studios Tech Talk, you will know what this involves.  In Tech, I will primarily be discussing interesting technology as I find it.
<strong>If a technology is useful in my life, I am sure it will be useful in somebody else&#39;s life</strong>.  I want to share that information in order to benefit you.</p>
<h4>Dev</h4>

<p>I expect this one to really only benefit software developers who stumble upon my site via Google.  In these I will be speaking of software development.
<strong>I may post about a problem I have solved or about a personal project I am working on</strong>.  Occasionally I have solved problems and thought, &quot;I could write a blog post about that.&quot;
If I have that thought, now I can!</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>

<p>There&#39;s the explanation for the new blog and the new site!  Please leave any feedback in a comment below!  Are there any topics you would like me to cover in the future?</p>
]]></description>
            <link>http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/first-post.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.tankstudios.net//posts/first-post.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 03:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>